jjill.com 2019-06-07

# Privacy Policy

February 1, 2019

At J.Jill, we understand your concerns about online security and privacy and appreciate the trust you place in our company. We seek to ensure that your personal and payment information is secure and that your privacy is respected. We hope this policy statement provides you with answers to the questions you may have about our policies. If you have further questions, please contact us by phone at **1.800.343.5700** or email us anytime. 

### information we collect

In order to provide the services you request, we ask you for certain kinds of personal information. 

For example, when you place an order on our site or over the phone, make a purchase at our stores, create an online account, visit our web site, sign up to receive emails from us, request to "chat" with a customer service associate, or send us an email, you provide us with certain personally identifiable information, such as your name, email address, postal address, phone number and credit or debit card number. In addition to this information, we also maintain a record of your purchases from jjill.com, our catalog, and our stores. 

If you participate in one of our promotions, contests, surveys, or provide product reviews, you may provide us with additional personal information such as your age or date of birth. 

In addition, for each visitor to the web site, our web server automatically collects the following non-personally-identifiable information: your Internet service provider's address, the referring URL, your browser type and version, and information on the pages you access on our site.  This information is collected using technology including cookies and pixel tags.  For more information on our use of cookies, please see the section below. ****

We may also collect information from other sources, including address verification services and market research services. We may combine information you provide with other information available to us from other sources, including demographic information. ****

### using information we collect 

At J.Jill, we want to provide you with the best possible shopping experience. When we take an order on the phone or when you make a purchase online or at a store, we use your information to process your purchase, answer questions you may have, mail catalogs to you, and provide you with periodic emails, mailings and phone calls about our merchandise and promotions. 

Currently, we also gather online information about your purchases and shopping activities to improve the content of our web site, to enhance your online shopping experience, to improve our product selection, and to use in future marketing and promotional activities for our web site, our catalogs and our J.Jill stores.  We may use this information to better understand your shopping preferences and provide you with more relevant offers, information and promotions. 

###  information we share with others 

In some instances, we use third party companies to provide services for us, including providing customer and Internet services, taking and fulfilling orders, conducting J.Jill promotions and surveys, assisting in maintaining and managing customer information, and communicating effectively with our customers. These third party companies are given access to the information they need to provide these services, and may use cookies in order to do so.

If you apply for the J.Jill credit card online, you provide the personal information needed to process your application (including your social security number) directly to Comenity Bank, the issuer and the administrator of the credit card program. If you apply for the J.Jill credit card by phone or in the stores, we collect that information from you and provide it to Comenity Bank. Comenity Bank is independent of J.Jill and has its own privacy and security policies. 

We may use third-party service providers to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet. They may collect anonymous information about your visits to our Web site, and your interaction with our products and services. They may also use information about your visits to this and other Web sites to more accurately target advertisements for goods and services. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by most major web sites. No personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process.   While www.jjill.com is not configured to recognize a “do not track” signal from you browser, you do have choices regarding behavioral advertising.  If you would like more information about this practice and your choices for opting out, [click here](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#!/).

From time to time, J.Jill may also share information collected, including our catalog mailing lists, with other reputable third-party organizations whose products or services we feel may be of interest to you. You may opt-out of this sharing if you choose.  If you would like more information about this practice and your choices for opting out, contact us by phone at 1.800.343.5700.

On rare occasions, we may disclose specific information upon governmental request, in response to a court order, or when required by law to do so. We may also share information with companies assisting in fraud protection or investigation. We do not provide information to these agencies or companies for marketing or commercial purposes. 

###  cookies

Cookies are a browser feature that assigns unique identification to your browser or mobile device. Cookies are typically stored on the hard drive of your computer or mobile device and are used by our Site to help us personalize your shopping experience and remember any preferences or other actions. For example, if you have placed items in your shopping cart, we may use cookies to keep those items in your cart for your future access. 

We may use cookies to recognize you when your return to our site, provide you with access to your account information and understand your use of our site so we can improve the site features and customize communications to you. We may also use a cookie to help confirm your receipt of, and response to, our emails and provide you with a customized experience. 

In addition, we may use technologies such as our own cookies to provide you with relevant online display advertising tailored to your interests. To opt out of our cookies used for this online advertising, [click here](http://dtmc.jjill.com/adinfo/choice/prod/?type=fpc&cid=61898&cname=J.Jill&cmagic=f9c016&clogo=61898.png&loc=us&lang=en-us). 

We also currently use the services of a marketing company to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how visitors use our site. To do this, we use web beacons and cookies provided by our marketing company on this web site. The type of information we collect includes the areas of the web site visited and information about transactions made. By supplementing our records, this information helps us learn which of our products most interest our customers, and what kinds of offers our customers like to see. We may also use the data collected by the marketing company to conduct specialized marketing programs. As a visitor to jjill.com, you may "opt out" of the collection by such company of such data. To opt out, go to <http://wwu.jjill.com/optout.html>.

You also have the option to refuse cookies altogether by turning them off in your browser. In order to disable cookies, please consult with your browser’s help section. If you do turn off cookies, you may not be able to use some of the benefits of our site. 

We use a tool called Google Analytics to collect information related to your browsing behavior on our website. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the [Google Analytics Terms of Use ](https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/) and the [ Google Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy). If you choose, you can opt out by downloading and installing the [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on.](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/)

We also use a tool called Facebook pixel which allows us to measure the effectiveness of our advertising by understanding the actions you take on our website. To learn more about Facebook ads and manage your preferences,[ click here.](https://www.facebook.com/ads/about/?entry_product=ad_preferences)

###  communication choices 

If you do not want to receive our emails, you may submit your request to unsubscribe directly at jjill.com. To access this feature, click here. In addition, if you have received an email from J.Jill, you may also respond with the word "unsubscribe" in the subject line, or follow the unsubscribe link included at the bottom of the email.

You may also email us anytime, or contact us by phone at **1.800.343.5700** , or via the mail at the following address: 

J.Jill, Customer Preference Service,   
P.O. Box 2006, 100 Birch Pond Drive,   
Tilton, NH 03276-9900. 

Please note, however, such requests may take up to 10 business days to process. 

To request that we remove your name from our postal mailing lists or calling lists, please call **1.800.343.5700**. You can also email us anytime, or write to us at: 

J.Jill, Customer Preference Service,   
P.O. Box 2006, 100 Birch Pond Drive,   
Tilton, NH 03276-9900. 

Please include your name, address and phone number or the mailing label from your catalog so that we can properly identify you. Please note, however, that you may receive additional mailings, but you can expect that to cease in 6-8 weeks. 

If you do not want J.Jill to share information about you with non-affiliated companies for direct marketing purposes, please call **1.800.343.5700**. You can also email us anytime, or write to us at: 

J.Jill, Customer Preference Service,   
P.O. Box 2006, 100 Birch Pond Drive,   
Tilton, NH 03276-9900. 

Please include your name and mailing address in the message. Please note, however, such requests may take up to 6-8 weeks to process.   
Please also note that when you order from us, we may still need to contact you with regard to questions or information about your order. 

###  security 

It is our intent to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you. We use a variety of current technologies and processes, including encryption, for protection of our customer data, including your transactional information. 

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need access to your personal information are granted access to perform their jobs. 

Your account is protected by your account password. We urge you to keep your password safe and confidential, and recommend that you log out of your account and close your browser window when you have finished your visit. 

If you are having trouble with your browser, please email us anytime, or chat now with a Customer Service representative, 7:00 a.m. to midnight ET, seven days a week.

### privacy of young children 

We are concerned about the privacy of young children and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from a child under 13 years of age. 

###  policy changes 

We may, from time to time, update or amend this privacy policy. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post those policy changes on our web site. If you are at all concerned about how your information is used, you may periodically check our web site for updates.
